mrrebates.com 2019-11-30

# Privacy Policy - Mr. Rebates

### Personal Data

Only a user's email address and postal address is collected when users provide registration to Mr. Rebates.

By registering with Mr. Rebates, you will be automatically subscribed to the Mr. Rebates' email newsletter that contains coupons and specials from the Mr. Rebates merchant base that may be of interest to you. All Mr. Rebates email newsletters can be opted out of by simply clicking on a link within each email to remove your email address from the list.

Email addresses and postal address information are not shared or sold to third-party marketers or third-party agencies.

When a rebate check is sent to a Mr. Rebates member, it is necessary for the member to supply his/her postal address. All postal address information is kept in the strictest confidence in our secure database system. Postal address information is not shared or sold to third parties.

As part of the registration process, postal address information is collected which may be used to send periodic mailings, postcards or other promotions solely from Mr. Rebates and no other third parties.

Personal information may be shared if a violation of the Mr. Rebates' terms or other website's terms have been violated in Mr. Rebates' sole discretion.

### Aggregated Information:

Aggregated information, such as which page users access or visit and information volunteered by users, is collected through various methods. For example, Mr. Rebates collects IP addresses. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web. Web servers (the computers that "serve up" Web pages) automatically identify your computer by its IP address, and when you request a page from Mr. Rebates, our servers log your IP address. Mr. Rebates only uses IP addresses for the purposes of web traffic analysis and trends.

### Use of Cookies

Mr. Rebates also uses cookies to store information. A cookie is a small data file that most major Web sites write to your hard drive for record keeping purposes when you visit them. Cookies allow Mr. Rebates to measure activity on the site and to improve your user experience, for example by remembering your passwords and viewing preferences.

You may occasionally get cookies from our cash back partner stores, which is standard in the Internet industry. Mr. Rebates does not control these cookies, and these cookies are not subject to Mr. Rebates' privacy policies. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies.

### To California Residents:

Mr. Rebates collects "personally identifiable" information (postal address) when a member registers or requests a rebate check. That information is not shared with any other third-party.

### Children and Privacy:

Mr. Rebates encourages parents and guardians to spend time with their children online, and to be fully familiar with the sites visited by their children.

**Individuals under 13:**

No information should be submitted to or posted on Mr. Rebates by users under the age of 13 years without the consent of their parent or guardian. Mr. Rebates does not provide any personally identifying information for users under the age of 13, regardless of its source, to any third party for any purpose whatsoever unless disclosed during collection.

**Individuals 13 through 17:**

Mr. Rebates requests that children under the age of 18 do not submit or post information to the site without a parent or guardian's consent.

### Referral Program:

If a member is referred by another Mr. Rebates' member, the original referrer is able to view the referral's order amount originating from Mr. Rebates. However, the store where the purchase occurred is masked for privacy purposes so the only information given is the aggregate sale amount for referral rebate purposes.

### Quick Cash Button: (Browser Extension)

Usage of the Quick Cash Button browser extension is subject to the same privacy policies as detailed previously on this page in the PERSONAL DATA, AGGREGATED INFORMATION and USE OF COOKIES section of this privacy policy.

The Browser Extension will visually prompt you to press a button on a Mr. Rebates' slider graphic to start your cash back shopping session. The Browser Extension may also alert you of cash back offers with respect to a product or brand appearing on your search results or other pages you visit across the web and prompt you to click the Mr. Rebates' slider graphic button to activate cash back.

When the Mr. Rebates' slider graphic button is clicked from the Browser Extension, it will set a cookie on the customer's computer through an affiliate network for the purpose of crediting cash back similar to the same mechanism used when starting a shopping session at the Mr. Rebates website. If cookies from a recent click session to an affiliate network or other similar tracking devices are already present on the customer's computer, the Browser Extension will not automatically overwrite those cookies and it is the customer's responsibility to activate cash back at the Mr. Rebates' website in the case that the Mr. Rebates' slider graphic is not activated for any reason.

The information stored from usage of the Browser Extension includes, but is not limited to, information about the coupons, sales and stores that a customer clicks through the Browser Extension. The Browser Extension may also collect and store information about the websites a customer views even when not interacting with the Browser Extension (General Browsing Data).  General Browsing Data includes, but is not limited, to URLs of web pages visited, general information about the visited web page, product searches, product search results, information about products added to cart, confirmation page details, and other product information. Mr. Rebates DOES NOT sell this General Browsing Data to any third party. You may turn off the General Browsing Data collection by uninstalling the Browser Extension. Use of the information collected by the Browser Extension is subject to the Terms and Conditions and the Privacy Policy of the Mr. Rebates' website.

The Browser Extension periodically communicates with the Mr. Rebates' servers to insure that the latest version of the browser extension is present on the customer's respective browser.  The Browser Extension is auto updated with no action needed from the customer when a new version is released. Mr. Rebates' reservers the right to add features or functions to the Browser Extension, but have no obligation to make available any subsequent versions or new features of the Browser Extension. 

### Links to Other Sites:

It is important to note that Mr. Rebates contains links to sites other than Mr. Rebates and that those sites may not follow the same privacy policies as Mr. Rebates.

Mr. Rebates reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time and users will be notified of any changes made. 

USE OF THIS SITE SIGNIFIES YOUR CONSENT TO THIS ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY AND THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE. IF YOU DISAGREE WITH ANY OF THE ABOVE POLICIES, YOUR ONLY RECOURSE IS TO DISCONTINUE USE OF THE MR. REBATES WEBSITE OR CLOSE YOUR ACCOUNT VIA CUSTOMER SERVICE.
